



Ayhan Hakan Tekir

• Address: Ardahan Caddesi Hasan Sinan Apartmani NO:4, 99000, morfou, Cyprus

Email address: ayhanhakantekir@gmail.com

Phone number: (+90) 5338718584

Date of birth: 07/01/1994 Nationality: Turkish

ABOUT ME

I have always motivated myself to learn new things education. My biggest motivation is the desire to learn new things. I started improve myself firstly youtube i make electronic music and shared. My education life time always research new things and I loved finding solutions. I developed with HTML and CSS at the beginner level before, then I focused on mobile application and i started university then i bought mac book then i install x code and develop simple apps.in example i developed 'todo' and 'calculator' apps. i improve myself coding with swift language as i show down below, and also i am interest SwiftUI language and improve my coding skills.

Best regards, I hope we are working together.

WORK EXPERIENCE

[01/08/2021 - 31/08/2021] **Mobile phone repairman**

Pawn Shop Lefkosa Technical Mobile Repairer

City: Lefkosia Country: Cyprus

Main activities and responsibilities:

I worked as the repair and technical support of broken devices and took care of the delivery of these devices with customers.

[01/10/2021 - 01/02/2022] **Handheld programmer**

Phone Stack Junior IOS Developer

City: Lefka

Country: Cyprus

Main activities and responsibilities:

I developed my graduation project idea and published it on the app store, and All i used

libraries listed below. Firebase Database Firebase Auth SDWebImage MessageKit Lottie-Animation

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

[01/01/2008 - 01/01/2013] **FL Studio**

YouTube Online Education

[01/01/2010 - 01/01/2012] **Adobe Photoshop**

Tomak Photography, Timuçin Tomak

[15/01/2011 - 01/01/2012] Adobe Premier Pro

Tomak Photography, Timuçin Tomak

[01/01/2011 - 01/01/2012] Adobe After Effect

Tomak Photography, Timuçin Tomak

[01/09/2012 - 15/06/2014] **Computer Programing**

Gaziantep University Associate Degree https://www.gantep.edu.tr/

Address: Turkey

[10/09/2017 - 15/02/2022] **Management Information System (M.I.S)**

Europian University of Lefke

Address: Cyprus

[01/11/2021 - 17/03/2022] IOS & Swift Complete IOS Development Bootcamp

Angela Yu https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-4d3fbc30-6e5e-4ecd-a73a-cd5d30bfcea4/

 $[\ 01/12/2021\ -\ 01/03/2022\]$ IOS 15 Basic to Expert Mobile Developing

Atıl Samancıoğlu https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-c4c28380-6170-4778-aa2a-bfe19f0af86b/

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Turkish

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING C1 READING C1 WRITING C1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION C1 SPOKEN INTERACTION C1

DIGITAL SKILLS

My Digital Skills

Microsoft Office | Microsoft Excel | Microsoft Word | Microsoft Powerpoint | Good listener and communicator | Skype | WhatsApp | instagram | Social Media/ Social Network | Adobe In Design and Photoshop | Adobe Premier Pro | Adobe After Effects | FL STUDIO | X code